Seamus Heaney papers, 1951-2004
Emory University
- Photographs, 1951-2003, Series 5; Boxes 90 – 93; OP1
  - Seamus Heaney portrait painted by Peter Edwards, color, June 1988 (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - Seamus Heaney publicity photograph by Jerry Bauer, black and white, ca. 1989 (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - Seamus Heaney [in his office at Harvard University?], ca. 1970s (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - Seamus Heaney publicity photographs by Giovanni Giovannetti, two black and white photographs, ca. 1990s (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - Seamus Heaney standing beside large tree, photographer: Robin Hiteshaw, three black and white snapshots, ca. 1990s (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - Seamus Heaney in pigsty, color snapshot, ca. 1990s (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Seamus Heaney laughing, color snapshot, ca. 1990s (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Seamus Heaney, black and white, ca. 1990s (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Seamus Heaney at Harvard, color, ca. 1990s (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Seamus Heaney, color snapshot, ca. 1990s (Box 90, Folder 33)
  - Seamus Heaney speaking at The Friends of Irish Studies dinner (Boston College), black and white, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Seamus Heaney at Standing Stones of Stenness (Orkney), black and white, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 35)
  - Seamus Heaney at Magdalen College (Oxford), color snapshot, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 36)
  - Seamus Heaney at Nobel Prize ceremony, Stockholm, color, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 37)
  - Seamus Heaney publicity photograph by Nancy Crampton, used for announcement of Heaney's Common Wealth Award of Distinguished Service (Literature) in 1997, black and white [other 1997 award winners also included] (Box 90, Folder 38)
  - Seamus Heaney at Yale University commencement, color, 24 May 1999 (Box 90, Folder 39)
  - Seamus Heaney at Troy Lecture/ University of Massachusetts (Amherst), three black and white photographs, 5 April 2000 (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - Seamus Heaney at the Second Krakow Meetings of Poets, five color snapshots, ca. November 2000 (Box 90, Folder 41)
  - Seamus Heaney at lectern color snapshot, 30 January 2001 (Box 90, Folder 42)
  - Seamus Heaney signing Electric Light, Oxford, photographer: Norman McBeath, black and white, 29 March 2001 (Box 90, Folder 43)
  - Seamus Heaney with spear, color snapshot, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 44)
  - Seamus Heaney, undated (Box 90, Folder 45)
  - Seamus Heaney with others
  - Seamus Heaney with other State Exhibition Winners: Robert McLaughlin, Seamus McGrotty and Pat [Deery?], St. Columb's College [Derry], black and white, 1951 (Box 90, Folder 46)
  - Seamus Heaney with group of unidentified individuals, ca. early 1960s (Box 90, Folder 47)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney and an unidentified individual, color snapshot ca. 1960s (Box 90, Folder 48)
  - Seamus Heaney with Queen's College (Belfast) classmates, black and white, ca. 1961 (Box 90, Folder 49)
  - Seamus Heaney with school children, Belfast, black and white, 1965 (Box 90, Folder 50)
  - Seamus Heaney with Richard Murphy and Terence O'Neill at launch of Stewart's The Ulster Crisis, Midland Hotel, 20 April 1967 (Box 90, Folder 51)
  - Seamus Heaney with Hugh MacDiarmid at Biggar, Lanarkshire, Scotland, two black and white photographs, 1970s (Box 90, Folder 52)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney, [Catherine Heaney?], and two unidentified individuals, ca. 1970 (Box 90, Folder 53)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney, color snapshot, June 1971 (Box 90, Folder 54)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney and two small children, Railway Slopes, Broagh, black and white, [1972] (Box 90, Folder 55)
  - Seamus Heaney with Michael Longley and Derek Mahon, Marie and Catherine Heaney ["In Their Element" tour], four color snapshots, ca. 1977 (Box 90, Folder 56)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney and luggage standing by park bench, photographer: Thomas Victor, black and white, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 57)
  - Seamus Heaney and Derek Mahon standing on patio, color snapshot, ca, 1980s (Box 90, Folder 58)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney, Paul Muldoon and small child, three color snapshots, ca. 1980s (Box 90, Folder 59)
  - Seamus Heaney with Seamus Deane, Brian Friel, Stephen Rea, David Hammond, and Tom Paulin [Field Day directors], black and white, ca. 1980s (Box 90, Folder 60)
  - Seamus Heaney with unidentified individual, black and white, ca. 1980 (Box 90, Folder 61)
  - Seamus Heaney with Ted Hughes and Charles Causley reading/judging entries in first Arvon International Poetry Competition, July 1980 (Box 90, Folder 62)
  - Seamus Heaney with Michael Holohan, Margaret Hamlin, Jo Gogins, and Jack Myers at a gathering in Dallas, three color photographs, 28 January 1993 (Box 90, Folder 63)
  - Seamus Heaney with Richard Ellmann, Marie Heaney, John Kelly, Keith Schuchard, John Stone, Christine Kelly, and Lou Stone at the home of Richard Ellmann in Oxford [Emory British Studies Program], August 1984 (Box 90, Folder 64)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney and Penny Fitzgerald at bedside of Robert Fitzgerald, color snapshot, ca. 1985 with two photographs: Seamus Heaney with Penny Fitzgerald, Richard Levin, Gerhard Gasper and unidentified individuals at Yale, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 65)
  - Seamus Heaney with Sr. M. Martina, color snapshot, 18 November 1985 (Box 90, Folder 66)
  - Seamus Heaney with Keith Schuchard, Rand Brandes, Ron Schuchard, John Bugge at the Schuchard barbecue pit, ca. 1985 (Box 90, Folder 67)
  - Seamus Heaney with James J. McAuley and Robert H. Jacob, color snapshot, ca. 1986 (Box 90, Folder 68)
  - Seamus Heaney with Field Day fund-raising team: Brian Friel, Seamus Deane, John Hume, and unidentified individual, Smith Bagley residence, Washington, D.C., color photograph, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 69)
  - Seamus Heaney with Field Day fund-raising team: Brian Friel, Seamus Deane, John Hume, and unidentified individual, Smith Bagley residence, Washington, D.C., black and white photograph, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 70)
  - Seamus Heaney with infant [Nicholas Ellsberg?]; Marie Heaney, two black and white snapshots, ca. 1987 (Box 90, Folder 71)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney and unidentified individuals at christening of Nicholas Ellsberg, seven color snapshots, ca. 1997 (Box 90, Folder 72)
  - Seamus Heaney with Alexandra Parker, Robert Crawford, Philip Hobsbaum, and Marie Heaney, ca. 1988 (Box 90, Folder 73)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney, Ron Schuchard, Keith Schuchard, and unidentified individuals in Atlanta for Ellmann Lectures at Emory University, eight color snapshots, March 1988 (Box 90, Folder 74)
  - Seamus Heaney at reception held at A l'Ecu de France in celebration of the one hundredth year of T.S. Eliot's birth, four color snapshots, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 75)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney and unidentified individuals at "May Day" picnic [Massachusetts], two color snapshots, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 76)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney seated on porch steps, color snapshot, ca. Spring 1989 (Box 90, Folder 77)
  - Seamus Heaney with John Montague and Liam O'Flynn on the occasion of Heaney's fiftieth birthday, Montague's sixtieth, Gate Theatre (Dublin), three black and white photographs by Poetry Ireland, 1989 (Box 90, Folder 78)
  - Seamus Heaney with Derek Walcott and Roscoe Lee Brown, black and white, ca. 1900s (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Seamus Heaney with Brian Friel and Ted Hughes at Guildhall reading, Derry, black and white [early 1990s?] (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Seamus Heaney with Brian Friel and Ted Hughes at Guildhall reading, Derry, color [early 1990s?] with printed copy of Prudential Awards for the Arts booklet with photograph on page 10 (Box OP1)
  - Seamus Heaney with Seamus Deane and Derek Walcott, color, ca. 1990s (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Seamus Heaney with unidentified individual, ca. 1990s (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Seamus Heaney at reading and signing book for unidentified individual, two color snapshots, ca. 1990s (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Seamus Heaney standing with Michael Longley in front of portraits of the two men, color, ca. 1990s1 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Seamus Heaney with Brian Friel, two color photographs, ca. 1990s (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Seamus Heaney with [Melvyn] Bragg, color photograph by Archant Norfolk Ltd., ca. 1990s (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Seamus Heaney with Derek Walcott and Paul Muldoon, ca. 1990s (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Seamus Heaney with Derek Walcott, Roscoe Lee Brown, and unidentified individuals, two black and white photographs, ca. 1990s (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney and Helen Vendler at Thomas Hardy's grave, St. Michael's Yard, Stinsford, two color snapshots, ca. 1990s (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney, Catherine Heaney, and dog, black and white snapshot, ca. 1990s (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Seamus Heaney with unidentified individuals on trip to Japan, four color snapshots, Summer 1990 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Seamus Heaney chatting with Eilean Ni Chuilleanain in a group of unidentified individuals, Faneuil Hall, Boston, color snapshot, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Seamus Heaney with unidentified individuals, 20 March 1991 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Seamus Heaney with unidentified individuals attending conference [Dublin?], three color snapshots, 18 July 1992 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Seamus Heaney with unidentified individuals at Goshen College social event, four color snapshots, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marianne McDonald, color snapshot, ca. 1993 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Seamus Heaney with Bernard O'Donoghue posing with sculpture of Patrick Kavanagh and at other Dublin sites, seven color snapshots, ca. 1993 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Seamus Heaney with Michael Parker, Sue Zlosnik, and unidentified individuals at reading/book signing, Liverpool Hope University College, four color photographs, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Seamus Heaney with Ulf Kirchdorfer at book signing at Richland, color snapshot, January 1993 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Seamus Heaney with Kenzaburo Oe and Attilio Bertolucci in Palermo (Italy) for the awarding of the Mandello Prize, black and white photograph by Glovanni Giovannetti, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Seamus Heaney acknowledging receipt of Premio Mondello in Palermo (Italy), black and white photograph by Glovanni Giovannetti, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Seamus Heaney at Irish Night [Oxford University?], twenty-four color snapshots, November 1993 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Seamus Heaney with unidentified individuals outside bookstore after reading, Harvard University, 2 two color snapshots, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney and unidentified individuals at Elizabeth Bay House in Sydney (Australia), four color snapshots, 2 October 1994 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney and unidentified individuals at Elizabeth Bay House in Sydney (Australia), four color snapshots, 2 October 1994 (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Visit from Jim and Adele Dalsimer and other unidentified individuals, ten color snapshots, Summer 1995 (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Seamus Heaney with President Mary Robinson at Ireland's presidential residence, Arus an Vachtarian, black and white photograph by Frank Fennell, September 1995 (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - Seamus Heaney with Catherine Heaney following his daughter's graduation from Trinity College, two black and white photographs, 13 November 1995 (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - Seamus Heaney with Catherine Heaney, Michael Heaney, Christopher Heaney, and unidentified individuals in Stockholm, three color snapshots, ca. November 1995 (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Seamus Heaney and other Nobel laureates at awards ceremony, Stockholm, color photograph by Pal Sommelius, 10 December 1995 (Box 91, Folder 32)
  - Seamus Heaney receiving Nobel Prize from Karl Gustaf in Stockholm, color photograph by Reportagebild, 10 December 1995 (Box 91, Folder 33)
  - Seamus Heaney with Donald R. Blake and unidentified individuals at Nobel Prize function in Stockholm, three color snapshots, December 1995 (Box 91, Folder 34)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney, St. Lucia Choir, and unidentified individuals in Stockholm, December 1995 (Box 91, Folder 35)
  - Seamus Heaney with unidentified individuals in Rotterdam, one color snapshot, ca. 1996 (Box 91, Folder 36)
  - Seamus Heaney shaking hands with unidentified cellist, color photograph by Gerald McCarthy, ca. 1996 (Box 91, Folder 37)
  - Seamus Heaney with Seamus Deane, Dublin, two black and white photographs taken by Allen MacWeeney for New Yorker, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 38)
  - Seamus Heaney and Felim Egan walking on Sandymount Strand, black and white RTE Stills photograph, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 39)
  - Seamus Heaney with Robert Pinsky, Charles Wright, Adam Zagajewski, Frank Bidart, John Ashbery, unidentified individuals, Thom Gunn, Derek Walcott, James Fenton, Paul Muldoon, and C.K. Williams at event celebrating fifty years of poetry at Farrar, Straus & Giroux, New York, New York, 18 September 1996 (Box 91, Folder 40)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney, Bertie Ahern, and Hillary Clinton, official White House photograph, color, 30 October 1997 (Box 91, Folder 41)
  - Seamus Heaney with Peter Fallon and unidentified individual standing in front of bookshop window, color snapshot, ca. 1998 (Box 91, Folder 42)
  - Seamus Heaney with Henri Cole, Helen Vendler, and unidentified individuals at dinner, three color snapshots, ca. 1998 (Box 91, Folder 43)
  - Seamus Heaney with Helen Vendler, Czeslaw Milosz, and unidentified individuals at conference in California, six color snapshots, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 44)
  - Trip to Japan, five color snapshots, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 45)
  - Seamus Heaney with Robert Pinsky, cutting cake to celebrate Heaney's 60th birthday, black and white photograph by Nancy Crampton, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 46)
  - Seamus Heaney with Vaclav Havel and unidentified individual around conference table, four color snapshots, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 47)
  - Seamus Heaney with Peter Skrzynecki in a bookshop, two color snapshots, 30 April 1999 (Box 91, Folder 48)
  - Seamus Heaney with Barbara C. Harris at Yale University commencement, color snapshot, 24 May 1999 (Box 91, Folder 49)
  - Seamus Heaney with Alan Greenspan and unidentified individual at Yale University, photographer: Joy Bush, ca. 24 May 1999 (Box 91, Folder 50)
  - Seamus Heaney with other individuals in academic robes at Yale University commencement, two color snapshots, 24 May 1999 (Box 91, Folder 51)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney at Glenveagh Gardens (County Donegal), color snapshot, 29 July [1999?) (Box 91, Folder 52)
  - Seamus Heaney with two unidentified individuals reading Beowulf on site of Hrothgar's Hall outside Copenhagen, color photograph by Erik Refner, 20 June 2000 (Box 91, Folder 53)
  - Seamus Heaney with other Nobel Laureates: Kenzaburo Oe (1994), Derek Walcott (1992), Nadine Gordimer (1991), Gunter Grass (1999), [Nobel laureate reunion?], color photograph by Scanpix, ca. 2000 (Box 91, Folder 54)
  - Seamus Heaney with Robert Pinsky, Charles Wright, Richard Howard, Galway Kinnell, Jorie Graham, Mark Stand, C.K. Williams and other unidentified individually at unknown event, photographer: Nancy Campton, ca. 2000 (Box 91, Folder 55)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney and President Bill Clinton and Hillary Clinton at the White House, two official White House color photographs by David Scull, 17 March 2000 (Box 91, Folder 56)
  - Seamus Heaney at honorary doctorate awards ceremony at Universite de Caen Basse-Normandie, 21 November 2000 (Box 91, Folder 57)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney, Dimetri [?], Des Lally and unidentified individual at Connemara (County Galway, Ireland), five color snapshots, 2001 (Box 91, Folder 58)
  - Seamus Heaney with Paul Muldoon at Oxford, black and white photograph by Norman McBeath, 23 January 2001 (Box 91, Folder 59)
  - Seamus Heaney, Tom Paulin, Bermard O'Donoghue posing for photographers during Oxford Literary Festival, black and white photograph by Norman McBeath, 29 March 2001 (Box 91, Folder 60)
  - Seamus Heaney with unidentified individuals in Oporto (Portugal), color snapshot, May 2001 (Box 91, Folder 61)
  - Seamus Heaney with Ashley, Chuck, and Austin Howard, color snapshot, ca. June 2001 (Box 91, Folder 62)
  - Seamus Heaney with Anthony Hecht, Maria Brodsky, Derek Walcott, Vladimir Gandelsman, Paul Muldoon, Glen Maxwell at poetry reading "Tribute to Joseph Brodsky" at Guggenheim Museum (New York), five black and white photographs by Yioing Chen-Josephson, December 2001 (Box 91, Folder 63)
  - Seamus Heaney with Helen Murphy on the occasion of Murphy's graduation and Heaney's receiving honorary doctorate at University of East Anglia, color snapshot, July 2002 (Box 91, Folder 64)
  - Seamus Heaney at the launch of Dennis O'Driscoll's Exemplary Damages, three color snapshots, ca. October 2002 (Box 91, Folder 65)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marie Heaney, Feng Yang, Liam O'Connell, and other unidentified individuals in Dublin, ca. 2003 (Box 91, Folder 66)
  - Seamus Heaney laughing with unidentified individual, undated (Box 91, Folder 67)
  - Seamus Heaney with Derek Walcott and Joseph Brodsky, color photograph, undated (Box 91, Folder 68)
  - Seamus Heaney with Derek Mahon and two unidentified individuals in a pub, black and white snapshot, undated (Box 91, Folder 69)
  - Seamus Heaney with Marianne [?], color snapshot, undated (Box 91, Folder 70)
  - Seamus Heaney at home with Marie and unidentified individual, undated (Box 91, Folder 71)
  - Seamus Heaney with Derek Mahon [in academic robes] and unidentified individual, color snapshot, undated (Box 91, Folder 72)
  - Others
  - Railway gang in the Netherlands, black and white photograph, ca. 1900 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Three individuals identified as Hugo, Mom, Sophia, color Polaroid snapshot, ca. 1980s (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Larry [Humelak?] at the Wood Bellaghy, color snapshot, 25 December 1983 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Will Parini, color snapshot 1984 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Karen Watton with students at Traiskirchen near Vienna, three color snapshots, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Margaret Russell, color snapshot, 21 March 1987 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - John Edward and Judith [?], color photograph, May 1989 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Tatsuo Murata and [wife?] in Japan, color snapshot, ca. 1990 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified man and woman, black and white snapshot, summer 1991 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Ercole Ugo D'Andrea, black and white photograph by Ennio Rucco (Lecce, Italy), 1991 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Selo Zagrade [translator of Heaney writings), black and white snapshot, September 1991 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Cathleen Quirk in Belfast, color snapshot, August 1992 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Caroline E. Barry, color snapshot, ca. 1993 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Susan Dodd with her dog, Elliot, on the beach at Ocracoke (North Carolina), color snapshot, May 1993 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Two children of Alfred Alcorn standing in front of television set, color snapshot, ca. 1993 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Nicholas, Catherine Day, Nina, and Peggy Ellsberg, five color snapshots, December 1994 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Claudia and Rob McCorkle/Shapiro, color snapshot, December 1994 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Clare Cavanaugh with infant son, Martin, color snapshot, ca. December 1994 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Philip Hobsbaum and Rosemary on porch of their home, color snapshot, ca. 1996 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Joseph Degre in Antwerp (Belgium), color snapshot, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Unidentified man walking on pier in Tobago, black and white photograph by Norman McBeath, January 1997 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Peter Balakian with Helen, Jamie, and Sophia Balakian, color snapshot, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Joan Ramsden and unidentified individual, two color snapshots, ca. August 1997 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Genevieve Gaunt [god-daughter of Valentina Polukhina], Newcastle (England), color snapshot, ca. 1998 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Caroline and Adam Discoll, color photograph, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - Michael Blumenthal with son, Noah, and wife in Blumenthal (Texas), ca. 1998 (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Darcy O'Brien, two dolor snapshots, ca. 1998 (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - Theresa Haney, Gabriel James Haney, and James Haney, color snapshot, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - David and Virginia Yip, two color snapshots, 28 February 1999 (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - Ron Schuchard, Keith Schuchard, A.S. Byatt, and unidentified individuals sitting around dining table, color snapshot, ca. March 1999 (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - Mae and Lela Oliver on trips to Oregon and Minnesota, five color snapshots, 1999-2000 (Box 92, Folder 31)
  - Pamela Todd with Izzy [?] and unidentified child, color snapshot, ca. 2000 (Box 92, Folder 32)
  - Group of unidentified individuals, color snapshot, ca. 2000 (Box 92, Folder 33)
  - Madeline Kiser with family, color snapshot, ca. 2000 (Box 92, Folder 34)
  - Paul Muldoon with Jean Hanff Korelitz and children, Dorothy and Asher, color snapshot, ca. 2000 (Box 92, Folder 35)
  - Sophie and Jamie Balakian in St Lucia, color snapshot, February 2000 (Box 92, Folder 36)
  - Imogene Stuart with her granite sculpture of Saint Kevin and the Blackbird, in Glendalough (County Wicklow, Ireland), color snapshot, Summer, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 37)
  - Engel family at Monroe Engle's 80th birthday gathering, color snapshot, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 38)
  - Two unidentified children on the beach, color snapshot, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 39)
  - Philip Hobsbaum, Peter Redgrove and Fiona Patterson on the occasion of Peter Redgrove's receiving honorary doctorate from Sheffield, color photograph by Penelope Shuttle, June 2001 (Box 92, Folder 40)
  - Jerry McElveen, color snapshot, ca. 2002 (Box 92, Folder 41)
  - Blake Harris Brandes, color photograph, 2002 (Box 92, Folder 42)
  - Suzy Hannon and son, John, color snapshot, ca. May 2002 (Box 92, Folder 43)
  - Maureen Connelly with her two dogs, Axl and Shamrock, color snapshot, ca. December 2002 (Box 92, Folder 44)
  - Jane and Jack [?], two color snapshots, undated (Box 92, Folder 45)
  - Mary and Ted [?] with three unidentified children in Japan; three color snapshots, undated (Box 92, Folder 46)
  - Roscoe Lee Browne and unidentified individuals reading onstage, four black and white photographs, undated (Box 92, Folder 47)
  - [Barrie Cooke], two color Polaroid snapshots, undated (Box 92, Folder 48)
  - Derek Mahon in academic robes, two color snapshots, undated (Box 92, Folder 49)
  - Charles [Monteith?], color snapshot by N. Dutton, undated (Box 92, Folder 50)
  - Kieran Murphy, childhood acquaintance of Seamus Heaney, black and white photograph, undated (Box 92, Folder 51)
  - Unidentified couple, black and white photograph, undated (Box 92, Folder 52)
  - "Uncle Hughie with his thrasher," color snapshot, undated (Box 92, Folder 53)
  - Objects
  - Sculptures by Carolyn Mulholland, ten color photographs 1970s (Box 92, Folder 54)
  - Photograph of pencil sketch of unknown individual by Dale Pung with a pencil sketch of Seamus Heaney, ca. 1979 (Box 92, Folder 55)
  - Binding for set of Bog Poems sheets made by Bernard Middleton, color snapshot, ca. 1983 (Box 92, Folder 56)
  - Detail of painting of Ted Hughes by Barrie Cooke, two color snapshots, ca. 1985 (Box 92, Folder 57)
  - Henry Pearson paintings from [1988?] exhibition, seven color photographs, ca. 1988 (Box 92, Folder 58)
  - Sculpture of bird by Stony Creek Studio, color photograph, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 59)
  - Portrait of Seamus Heaney by John McConnell, color snapshot, ca. 1992 (Box 92, Folder 60)
  - Collection of objects including a check for ten thousand pounds, color snapshot, 1993 (Box 92, Folder 61)
  - Photograph taken in an electron microscope of a double helical protein structure, black and white, ca. 1993 (Box 92, Folder 62)
  - Rotting boat dry-docked in field off Old Glenn Highway [Eagle River, Alaska?], color snapshot, ca. May 1994 (Box 92, Folder 63)